wroupon.com 2015-05-24

# Privacy Policy| Groupon Clone Script |Group Buying Features | DealPHP.com Previously Wroupon

Groupon Clone

**Privacy policy to protect you and us!**

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This policy covers how DealPhp treats personal information that DealPhp collects and receives, including information related to your past use of DealPhp products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that DealPhp does not own or control, or to people that DealPhp does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**

**General**

  * DealPhp collects personal information when you register with DealPhp, when you edit your DealPhp profile. When you register we may ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code,. For some services we may also ask for your address, and other Server information. Once you register with DealPhp and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * DealPhp keep information about your transactions safe with us including 
  * DealPhp automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, DealPhp cookie information, and the page you request. 

**Children**

  * DealPhp does not allow a child under age 13 to register with our services. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * DealPhp does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of DealPhp's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if DealPhp is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, DealPhp will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

**Cookies**

  * DealPhp may set and access DealPhp cookies on your computer. 

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**  
**General**

  * You can edit your DealPhp Account Information at any time. 
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the DealPhp Product and service , such as Product announcements, administrative messages and the DealPhp Newsletter, that are considered part of your DealPhp account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 
  * You can delete your DealPhp account by contact us 

  * 

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * DealPhp may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your DealPhp account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please send us an e-mail to **admin at DealPhp.com** or you can contact us at: 

DealPhp, Inc. Lafayette Park Street ,

Los angeles ,California 90057  
admin-at-DealPhp.com

  *[Groupon Clone]: Dealphp.com
